{
    "id": "34eed437a92744b6b8296a34c4668e0f",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I haven’t invited ……………………….. them.",
            "description": "We use either of before a pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "either of",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "392bf8fc7f67441488e796cd07ea9476"
        },
        {
            "question": "If either of the girls phones, tell ……………………… that I am busy.",
            "description": "A pronoun used to refer back to either + noun / pronoun can be singular or plural.",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "them",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa2aef23fab440a7b427e7bdb3eab2a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hit the target ……………………… in the middle.",
            "description": "When right is used before a preposition referring to place or movement, it means completely or exactly.",
            "answers": [
                "right",
                "rightly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d5f3ba44ea184c9c841ed14ae251aaf6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had ……………………… a thunderstorm last night.",
            "description": "We can use quite with singular countable nouns to express the idea that something is remarkable. Rather is not possible with this meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "quite",
                "quiet"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8f245c4dbc224be0ae2faea2e669ac11"
        },
        {
            "question": "She hasn’t got ……………………… for the job.",
            "description": "As an adjective enough goes before the noun modified by it.",
            "answers": [
                "experience enough",
                "enough experience"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "85dd72df69094a53a904843fc15210af"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although my grandfather is eighty-five, he enjoys ………………………….",
            "description": "Health is an uncountable noun we cannot use the article ‘a’ with it.",
            "answers": [
                "good health",
                "a good health",
                "the good health"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6a65292fbe554ba7ad989f999518f181"
        },
        {
            "question": "The house …………………….. I live in is very spacious.",
            "description": "That…in means the same as where.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ff29fa3efdd428790fed3baff9ccee7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Because I was ill for six months, …………………….. lost my job.",
            "description": "Use so or because in a sentence. Don’t use them both.",
            "answers": [
                "as I",
                "so I",
                "I"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5088cb33a2e84f9ca35f86314476e5ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul lives in ………………….",
            "description": "We do not normally use the with singular proper names.",
            "answers": [
                "Italy",
                "the Italy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4fb66753b6fd423981c94af9eda5bcda"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. child can learn to swim.",
            "description": "Any and every can both be used to talk in general about all the members of a class or group.",
            "answers": [
                "Any",
                "Every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "18e6ae85c96e4701be4e25c15527d18b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ………………………. happy and sad.",
            "description": "Alternately means in turn.",
            "answers": [
                "alternatively",
                "alternately",
                "alternative",
                "alternate"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c377a6af5054c06bf041e09b20a94ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. I didn’t understand a word, I kept smiling.",
            "description": "Even if refers to the present or future. Even though refers to the past.",
            "answers": [
                "Even though",
                "Even if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fe6cde54c9654e52a05609d39bb7fb88"
        }
    ]
}